

# **DAVID CANO ZAFRA**

IPHYSICS ENGINEER, DATA SCIENTIST AND ENGINEER

**ADRESS** 

C/ MARÍA GUZMÁN, MADRID

**NUMBER** 629985034

E-MAIL

DAVID.CANO221@GMAIL.COM

WEBPAGE: HTTPS://DAVIDCANO221.GITHUB.IO/DAVIDCANO/

## **PROFESSIONAL PROFILE**

Physics engineer specializing in Data Science and Engineering. 1-year experience analyzing digital biomedical signals, and a Master in Biomedical Engineering/Data Processing. I consider myself a curious person willing and able to learn fast and constantly improve. I can adapt to different scenarios providing perspectives from the mathematical, physics, and engineering fields.

## **EDUCATION**

MSC DATA SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING CURRENTLY

WEBPAGES CREATION, PROGRAMMING, AND DESIGN 2020

E-LEARNING TRAINING 2020

MSC BIOMEDICAL ENGINEERING 2018 - 2020

BSC PYSHICS ENGINEERING 2014 - 2018

## **LANGUAGES**

SPANISH
CATALAN
ENGLISH
GERMAN

## **PROGRAMMING SKILLS**



**PYTHON** 



R



**MATLAB** 



**EXCEL** 



**SQL** 



NOSQL



**TABLEAU** 



**POWER BI** 

### **EXPERIENCE**

DATA SCIENTIST - HOSPITAL VALL D'HEBRON CURRENTI Y

- Data preprocessing with Dataflows and Power Automate.
- Creation of visualizations with Power BI.
- Statistical analysis with Python and R.

#### **RESEARCHER - UPC**

SEPT. 2018 - JAN. 2020

- Acquisition, filtering and visualization of digital biomedical signals.
- Utilization of Matlab and Python.

#### STUDENT SUPPORT - UPC

MAR. 2018

 To inform college students who are interested in the degree about the features of it.

#### **CUSTOMER SUPPORT - DECATHLON**

JUNE 2017 - SEPT. 2017

- To attend and support the customer.
- To help the teammates of other departments.

#### PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

VERSATILITY RESPONSIBILITY

WILLINGNES TO PROBLEM LEARN SOLVING

ASSERTIVENESS TEAMWORK